{"data":[{"question":"Pupils are learning ________.","a":"English","b":"England","c":"in English","d":"in England","answer":"1","explain":"\n- English (noun): the language used in Britain, the US, Australia, and some other countries.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Let's play football. Yes, ________.","a":"lets","b":"we play","c":"let us do","d":"let's","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Let's = let us.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Her birthday is ________ November.","a":"in","b":"on","c":"at","d":"into","answer":"1","explain":"\n- In: used as a preposition followed by a noun ( month)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Maria is ________ the radio.","a":"looking","b":"watching","c":"listening to","d":"hearing to","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Listen to sbd\/ sth (we say listen to radio).\u00a0\n- Hear sbd\/sth.\u00a0\n- Looking at.\u00a0\n- Watch bdd\/sth (often say \"watch TV\").","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Let's go out to play now. No, ________ I am doing my homework.","a":"all right","b":"let's not","c":"we don't","d":"let's","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Let's not do sth: used to refuse the suggestion","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"My young brother can sing but I ________.","a":"aren't","b":"can","c":"can't","d":"am not","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Can't: negative form of can.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"When's your birthday? \nIt's ________.","a":"in 1990","b":"on May 20th","c":"in October","d":"in May 20th","answer":"2","explain":"\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on, between, over, into.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"________ Mr.Baker want a new raincoat?","a":"Does","b":"Do","c":"Can","d":"Must","answer":"1","explain":"- We need a auxiliary before a singular noun in present simple tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The weather is hot in Vietnam ________.","a":"in winter","b":"in summer","c":"in spring","d":"in autumn","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The weather is usually hot in summer ( a fact)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"________ a lot of other people, we managed to survive the recession.","a":"Contrary to","b":"In contrast to","c":"On the contrary with","d":"In contrast with","answer":"2","explain":"\n- In contrast to sbd\/sth: a difference between people, ideas, situations, things etc that are being compared.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}